Blondell Hill Gospel Music Collection, circa 1916-1964 SC 158
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 2. Ephemera, 1950-1958; undated; 3 Folders
  - Postcards from Harbor Springs, Michigan, undated; 4 postcards
    - Overlooking Harbor Point and Petoskey - Harbor Springs, Mich., undated; 1 postcard
      Online Access
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000002
      Shelf Number
      PA005302
    - Little Traverse Bay - Harbor Springs, Mich., undated; 1 postcard
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000003
      PA005303
    - Sunset - Harbor Springs, Michigan, undated; 1 postcard
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000004
      PA005304
    - "The Pointer" - Harbor Point, Michigan, undated; 1 postcard
      Image Online
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000005
      PA005305
  - Programs and Miscellaneous Papersundated., 1950-1953; 2 concert programs; 1 receipt; 1 photocopy (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Annual Sacred Concert, The First Methodist Church, Harbor Springs, Michigan, August 23, 1953; 1 program (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Rental Book Fee Receipt, Hibberd School, January 23, 1950; 1 receipt (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Civic Music Association Presents Floyd Worthington, undated; 1 program (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Photocopy of Acts 1:12 through 2:28 page from unidentified bible, undated; 1 document photocopy (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photograph of the Petoskey, Michigan Volunteer Gospel Choir, 1958; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    Included in picture are both Blondell Hill and her daughter Rochelle.
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-000001
    PA005301